<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Playlog on micro.pinapelz.moe</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/playlog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Playlog on micro.pinapelz.moe</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>yukais@pinapelz.com (Pinapelz)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>yukais@pinapelz.com (Pinapelz)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:15:50 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/playlog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Playlog: FFXIV Dawntrail Patch 7.4 Thoughts (spoilers)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-12-19-08-ffxiv-patch-7-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:15:50 -0800</pubDate><author>yukais@pinapelz.com (Pinapelz)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-12-19-08-ffxiv-patch-7-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is primarily focused on the content of the patch, not so much the features they&amp;rsquo;ve added.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;story&#34;&gt;Story&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mistwake Dungeon was a good difficulty. Although I&amp;rsquo;m not a fan of the electricity star AOEs, very hard to read for no apparent reason. Please just stick with the old one.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cutscene quality def. got better. As in animations and uniqueness.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Love the look and feel (Treno). There&amp;rsquo;s a ton of good spots for &amp;ldquo;gpose-ing&amp;rdquo;. Music is nice too.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Seriously Krile? You parents were the ones who dropped you into the Source. I don&amp;rsquo;t think they&amp;rsquo;d care if you wanted to stay in the Source (just make up your mind) -&amp;gt; well glad that got sorted out&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hell on Rails&amp;rdquo; Trial (Doomtrain) is very nicely designed. Its got some nice unique mechanics, the &amp;ldquo;sucking&amp;rdquo; mechanic definetly trips you up the first time because the distance to move back + timing has been tuned so that you need to pre-position for it.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The transition from inside the engine to outside was really cool!!! This is probably one of my top normal trials now.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The instance battle was well done too. The roleplaying part was on point, and when it was finally time to fight a real boss you get to play as yourelf (I think this is the best flow). Love the idea using the spriggan to avoid Behemoth&amp;rsquo;s meteor.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cool so we just get to keep the key. If this were any bit realistic, we&amp;rsquo;ve surely learned that no one this powerful should be allowed to keep the key on themsleves 24/7. Because surely the WoL being the most powerful being will never run rogue with a interdimensional travel capable tool. Then again, seeing how stuff gets stolen all the time in the story&amp;hellip; Well I guess it can go either way.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m guessing this key is gonna be how the writers justify being able to travel to new worlds for post-Zodiark/Hydaelyn story. Its fine I guess, but a little disappointing it isn&amp;rsquo;t something more unique.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;And what do you know. Ascians. I hope we get something unqiue for 8.0&amp;hellip; I guess thats fine but please lets not have it just be SHB all over again.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;raid&#34;&gt;Raid&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;Feral Fandom&amp;rdquo; -&amp;gt; Yep thats FF14 NA playerbase for you.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Heavyweight 1 (Vamp Fatale) Raid was cool and unique, but a bit too flashy imo. That Half Moon is needlessly large, wish we&amp;rsquo;d stop with mechanics that are designed to trick people even when read correctly.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Heavyweight 2 (Xtremes) I take it back, this is the one with the blinding effects MY EYES. Fire and water one after another. This is a pretty hard normal fight actually (the first time you run it blind). Really punishing for bad AOE placement positions since you can effectively be cut off from the team.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Holy wow these cutscenes are in serious need of voice acting. Its a good story but so dry and awkward without it.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Heavyweight 3 (Tyrant). Really? Behemoth again, double dipping from the instance battle. There&amp;rsquo;s so many other cool FF monsters. I like the arena, it fits the guy well, all about history of the Arcadion/tradition. Fight is underwhelming and too easy imo, apart from 1 single trick mechanic that can cause a wipe&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Heavyweight 4 (Lindwurm). EVERYTHING BURNS. This fight was honestly too easy, zero deaths everything can be read. 2nd phase was underhelming.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Overall the story here while not as in depth and relevant to the story as Endwalker raids, still had a nice little twist at the end I def did not expect. Enjoyed it!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;misc&#34;&gt;Misc&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The new Frontline map is &amp;ldquo;dangerous&amp;rdquo;. Overall the new capturing point system is far better than a non-interruptable interact like in Onsal Hakir. The snowman and aurora events are also good, and I think they come in right when they&amp;rsquo;re needed too (to spice things up/allow for a turning point).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The map design however is far too complex, all these bridges and everywhere and invisible walls. It does add a lot of chokepoints but also makes it difficult to navigate from point A -&amp;gt; B (but partially I guess this is done cause the map does feel smaller than Onsal).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313//tags/ffxiv&#34; class=&#34;p-category&#34;&gt;#ffxiv&lt;/a&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
